yithemes.com 2017-12-28

# Cookie policy

High Quality Free WordPress Themes  
And Plugins For WooCommerce 

## Extended Cookie Policy

Cookies consist of portions of code installed in the browser that assist the Owner in providing the service according to the purposes described. Some of the purposes for which the Cookies are installed may also require the User’s consent. 

### Technical Cookies and Cookies serving aggregated statistical purposes

  * ### Activity strictly necessary for the functioning of the service

This Application uses Cookies to save the User’s session and to carry out other activities that are strictly necessary for the operation of the same, for example in relation to the distribution of traffic. 

  * ### Activity regarding the saving of preferences, optimization, and statistics

This Application uses Cookies to save browsing preferences and to optimize the User’s browsing experience. Among these Cookies are, for example, those to set the language and the currency or for the management of first party statistics employed directly by the Owner of the site. 

### Other types of Cookies or third-party tools that might use them

Some of the services listed below collect statistics in aggregated form and may not require the consent of the User or may be managed directly by the Owner – depending on how they are described – without the help of third parties. If any third party operated services are listed among the tools below, these may be used to track Users’ browsing habits – in addition to the information specified herein and without the Owner’s knowledge. Please refer to the privacy policy of the listed services for detailed information. 

  * ### Analytics

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior. 

#### Google Analytics (Google Inc.)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data. Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

  * ### Content performance and features testing (A/B testing)

The services contained in this section allow the Owner to track and analyze the User response concerning web traffic or behavior regarding changes to the structure, text or any other component of this Application. 

#### Google Website Optimizer (Google Inc.)

Google Website Optimizer is an A/B testing service provided by Google Inc. Google may use Personal Data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data. Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/)

  * ### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

This type of services allow interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Application. The interaction and information obtained through this Application are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network. This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it. 

#### Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)

The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc. Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data. Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

#### Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter)

The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter Inc. Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data. Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/privacy)

#### Google+ +1 button and social widgets (Google Inc.)

The Google+ +1 button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Google+ social network provided by Google Inc. Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data. Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/)

  * ### RSS feed management

This type of services allows this Application to manage RSS feeds and the distribution of their content. Depending on the characteristics of the service used, these services may be used to insert ads within the content and to gather statistics data from them. 

#### Feedburner (Google)

Feedburner is a service to manage RSS feeds provided by Google Inc. It allows the collection of statistics on what content is consumed and to insert ads in it. Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data. Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

### How can I manage the installation of Cookies?

In addition to what is specified in this document, the User can manage preferences for Cookies directly from within their own browser and prevent – for example – third parties from installing them. Through the browser preferences, it is also possible to delete Cookies installed in the past, including the Cookies that might possibly have saved the consent for the installation of Cookies by this website. It is important to note that by disabling all Cookies, the functioning of this site may be compromised. Users can find information about how to manage Cookies in their browser at the following addresses: [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&p=cpn_cookies), [Mozilla Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences), [Apple Safari](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?viewlocale=en_US&locale=en_US) and [Microsoft Windows Explorer](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-vista/block-or-allow-cookies). In the case of services provided by third parties, Users can exercise their right to withdraw from the tracking activity by utilizing the information provided in the third party’s privacy policy, by clicking the opt-out link – if provided – or by contacting the third party. Notwithstanding the above, the Owner informs that Users may take advantage of: [Your Online Choices](https://www.youronlinechoices.com/). This service allows Users to select their tracking preferences for most of the advertising tools. The Owner thus recommends that Users make use of this resource in addition to the information provided in this document. 

### Data Controller and Owner

Your Inspiration S.L.U. – Avenida Buenos Aires, Santa Cruz de Tenerife, Tenerife, 38005 – Spain Since the installation of third party Cookies and other tracking systems through the services used within this Application can not be technically controlled by the Owner, any specific references to Cookies and tracking systems installed by third parties are to be considered indicative. In order to obtain complete information, consult the privacy policy for the respective third party services listed in this document. Given the objective complexity linked to the identification of technologies based on Cookies and their very close integration with the operation of the web, Users are encouraged to contact the Owner should they wish to receive any further information on the use of Cookies themselves and any possible use of them – for example, by a third party – carried out through this site. 

### Definitions and legal references

#### Personal Data (or Data)

Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number. 

#### Usage Data

Information collected automatically from this Application (or third party services employed in this Application), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Application, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User’s IT environment. 

#### User

The individual using this Application, which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refers. 

#### Data Subject

The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers. 

#### Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization authorized by the Data Controller to process the Personal Data in compliance with this privacy policy. 

#### Data Controller (or Owner)

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Application. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Application. 

#### This Application

The hardware or software tool by which the Personal Data of the User is collected. 

#### Cookies

Small piece of data stored in the User’s device. 

* * *

#### Legal information

Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies. 

### ABOUT US

We develop innovative WordPress themes and plugins for e-commerce, portfolio, corporate sites, blogs and communities. We are among the ThemeForest Top Sellers and for years our philosophy has been based on simplicity, beauty and 100% effectiveness. To show it, we offer a free version of our products to the users.

Payment Options
